Fulton Lewis Jr. Papers
Fulton Lewis Jr. Papers
- Part I. Audiovisual material
  - Films
    - Fulton Lewis Jr. Show (2), lewis_f_jr_0502; Old label is inserted in the can. It reads: “Fulton Lewis Jr. Promo No. 2. To Mr. Raymond Brown, WTRI, P. O. Box 4035, Albany, NY”. Label glued underneath reads: “Fulton Lewis Jr. No. 2A”.; Film: 16mm
    - Fulton Lewis Production No. 3, lewis_f_jr_0444; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Fulton Lewis, JR - Pilot Show, lewis_f_jr_0427; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Germany (1), lewis_f_jr_0075; Film: 16mm
    - Germany (2), lewis_f_jr_0076; Film: 16mm
    - Germany (3), lewis_f_jr_0077; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Germany (4), lewis_f_jr_0078; Film: 16mm
    - Grace Line #1, lewis_f_jr_0093; Film: 16mm, color
    - Greece - Milt Hammer (Series C, No. 6), lewis_f_jr_0432; produced by Pearson Productions; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Guatemala, 01/16/1954; lewis_f_jr_0053; Film: 16mm
    - Guatemala, lewis_f_jr_0437; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Guatemala, lewis_f_jr_0438; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Guatemala, lewis_f_jr_0460; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Guatemala, lewis_f_jr_0477; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Guatemala (1), lewis_f_jr_0079; Film: 16mm
    - Guatemala (2), lewis_f_jr_0080; Film: 16mm
    - Guatemala (3), 1954; lewis_f_jr_0081; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Guatemala (4), lewis_f_jr_0082; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Guatemala (5), lewis_f_jr_0083; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Guatemala (6), lewis_f_jr_0084; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Guatemala (7), 07/29/1955; lewis_f_jr_0085; Film: 16mm
    - Hearings #2, 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0094; Film: 16mm, b/w, running time 11:40
    - Heart, lewis_f_jr_0086; Film: 16mm
    - Heart (1), 07/26/1955; lewis_f_jr_0095; Film: 16mm
    - Heart (2), lewis_f_jr_0096; Film: 16mm
    - Heart (3), lewis_f_jr_0097; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Idlewild, lewis_f_jr_0435; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Idlewild, lewis_f_jr_0446; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Idlewild, lewis_f_jr_0507; Note on the old leader reads: “Fulton Lewis (No. 20), Washington video”. Accompanying the film is old tape, note reads: “Reel No. 7 Show”.; Film: 16mm
    - Idlewild (1), lewis_f_jr_0087; Film: 16mm
    - Idlewild (2), lewis_f_jr_0088; Film: 16mm
    - Idlewild (3), lewis_f_jr_0089; Film: 16mm
    - Indo China (1), lewis_f_jr_0090; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - International Air Travel, lewis_f_jr_0456; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - International Air Travel, lewis_f_jr_0472; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - International Air Travel, 1954; lewis_f_jr_0504; Note on the leader reads: “Fulton Lewis Jr. No. 21”. Illegible old label from the leader is inserted in the can.; Film: 16mm
    - Investigation of Investigations, 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0103; Film: 16mm, b/w, running time 11:45
    - Japan (1), 03/16/1955; lewis_f_jr_0098; Film: 16mm
    - Japan (2), lewis_f_jr_0099; Film: 16mm
    - Japan (3), lewis_f_jr_0100; Film: 16mm
    - Japan (4), 02/04/1955; lewis_f_jr_0101; Film: 16mm
    - Japan (5), 03/22/1955; lewis_f_jr_0102; Film: 16mm
    - Japan (1), lewis_f_jr_0104; Film: 16mm
    - Japan (2), lewis_f_jr_0105; Film: 16mm
    - Japan (3), lewis_f_jr_0106; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Japan (4), lewis_f_jr_0107; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Japan (5), lewis_f_jr_0108; Film: 16mm
    - Japan (6), lewis_f_jr_0109; Film: 16mm
    - Japan (7), lewis_f_jr_0110; Film: 16mm
    - Japan (Fulton Lewis #7), lewis_f_jr_0430; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Jr’s Achievement, lewis_f_jr_0440; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Junior Achievement, lewis_f_jr_0111; Film: 16mm
    - Junior Achievement, lewis_f_jr_0475; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Junket #1, lewis_f_jr_0112; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland, lewis_f_jr_0469; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Knowland, lewis_f_jr_0482; produced by WALA-TV; General Teleradio Film Division; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Knowland (1), lewis_f_jr_0113; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (2), lewis_f_jr_0114; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (3), lewis_f_jr_0115; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (4), lewis_f_jr_0116; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (5), lewis_f_jr_0117; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (6), lewis_f_jr_0118; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (7), lewis_f_jr_0119; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (1), lewis_f_jr_0120; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (2), lewis_f_jr_0121; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (3), 03/21/1955; lewis_f_jr_0122; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (4), lewis_f_jr_0123; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (5), lewis_f_jr_0124; Film: 16mm
    - Knowland (6), lewis_f_jr_0125; Film: 16mm
    - Land Reform (1), lewis_f_jr_0130; Film: 16mm
    - Land Reform (2), lewis_f_jr_0131; Film: 16mm
    - Lie Detector, 04/02/1954; lewis_f_jr_0480; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Lie Detector, 1954; lewis_f_jr_0519; Note on the original leader reads: “#13, Lie Detector”. Copy of the old can label is accompanying the film.; Film: 16mm
    - Lie Detector (1), lewis_f_jr_0126; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Lie Detector (2), lewis_f_jr_0127; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Lie Detector (3), 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0128; Film: 16mm, b/w, running time 11:13
    - Lie Detector (4), May 2 [no year]; lewis_f_jr_0129; Film: 16mm
    - Manpower and Defense, 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0132; Film: 16mm, b/w, running time 12:00
    - Manpower and Defense, No. 8, 1954; lewis_f_jr_0497; Note on the leader reads: “F Lewis Jr. No. 5. Wash. Video”.; Film: 16mm
    - McCarthy-Stevens Hearings, 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0054; Film: 16mm, b/w, running time 11:50
    - MPTV - (Drew) Pearson Series (B14): Friendship, lewis_f_jr_0505; Film: 16mm
    - N. I. H. - Heart, lewis_f_jr_0516; Note on the leader reads: “Fulton Lewis Jr. No. 19”. Inserted in the can are the hold-down masking tapes.; Film: 16mm
    - Narcotics, lewis_f_jr_0425; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Narcotics - No. 1, lewis_f_jr_0434; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Narcotics (1), lewis_f_jr_0133; Film: 16mm
    - Narcotics (2), lewis_f_jr_0134; Film: 16mm
    - Narcotics (3), lewis_f_jr_0135; Film: 16mm
    - Narcotics (1), lewis_f_jr_0139; Film: 16mm
    - Narcotics (2), 1955; lewis_f_jr_0140; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Narcotics (3), lewis_f_jr_0141; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Narcotics (1), lewis_f_jr_0476; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Narcotics (2), lewis_f_jr_0463; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Narcotics No. 2, lewis_f_jr_0447; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Narcotics (1), lewis_f_jr_0515; Note on the leader reads: “Fulton Lewis Jr. No. 22”.; Film: 16mm
    - Narcotics (2), lewis_f_jr_0500; Note on the leader reads: “Fulton Lewis Jr. No. 23”; Film: 16mm
    - New Weapons, lewis_f_jr_0136; Film: 16mm
    - Nike Missile, 1954; lewis_f_jr_0137; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - One Year Later - Mayan coffee, bananas, corn, lewis_f_jr_0411; produced by KHJ-TV; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Oppenheimer, 06/11/1954; lewis_f_jr_0138; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Oppenheimer, lewis_f_jr_0457; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Pan American Highway, lewis_f_jr_0471; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Pan American Highway, 1954; lewis_f_jr_0510; Note on the leader reads: “No. 26”.; Film: 16mm
    - (Drew) Pearson Production Series “C” No. 7: Strohm - Milt Hammer (Russian farmers interview), lewis_f_jr_0511; Film: 16mm
    - Pearson, Drew (1), lewis_f_jr_0142; Film: 16mm
    - Pearson, Drew (2), lewis_f_jr_0143; Film: 16mm
    - Pearson, Drew (3), lewis_f_jr_0144; Film: 16mm
    - Pearson, Drew (4), lewis_f_jr_0145; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Pearson, Drew (5), lewis_f_jr_0146; Film: 16mm, color
    - Peterboro (1), lewis_f_jr_0147; Film: 16mm, color
    - Picket Ship, lewis_f_jr_0467; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Picket Ship, lewis_f_jr_0478; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Picket Ship (1), lewis_f_jr_0148; Film: 16mm
    - Picket Ship (2), lewis_f_jr_0149; Film: 16mm
    - Picket Ship (3), lewis_f_jr_0150; Film: 16mm
    - Picket Ship (4), lewis_f_jr_0151; Film: 16mm
    - Picket Ship (5), 03/21/1955; lewis_f_jr_0152; Film: 16mm
    - Picket Ship (6), lewis_f_jr_0153; Film: 16mm
    - Pickett Ship, lewis_f_jr_0412; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Placid Harbor (1), lewis_f_jr_0154; Film: 16mm, color
    - Placid Harbor (2), lewis_f_jr_0166; Film: 16mm, color
    - Placid Harbor (3), lewis_f_jr_0167; Film: 16mm, color
    - (Production 2), 01/17/1954; lewis_f_jr_0484; produced by KPRC-TV; Wm. Dolph Radio Productions Inc.; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - (Production 2), lewis_f_jr_0485; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - (Production 2), lewis_f_jr_0488; produced by KFDA-TV; Washington Video Productions, Inc.; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - (Production 2), lewis_f_jr_0490; broadcast info card was inserted into the canister; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - (Production 2), lewis_f_jr_0513; Note on the leader reads: “Fulton Lewis Jr. Prod. No. 2”.; Film: 16mm
    - (Production 3), lewis_f_jr_0486; produced by KDOB-TV; Washington Video Productions Inc.; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - (Production 3), lewis_f_jr_0489; produced by WPMT-TV;; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - (Production 3), lewis_f_jr_0498; Film: 16mm
    - [Fulton Lewis, Jr. 6], 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0487; produced by Washington Video Productions Inc.; script for "Fulton Lewis, Jr. TV Program # 4" is inserted in the canister.; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Puerto Rico (1), 05/19/1954; lewis_f_jr_0161; Film: 16mm, running time 11:30
    - Puerto Rico (2), 03/25/1954; lewis_f_jr_0169; Film: 16mm, b/w, running time 11:30
    - Quemoy, 1954; lewis_f_jr_0170; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Quemoy (1), lewis_f_jr_0155; Film: 16mm
    - Quemoy (2), lewis_f_jr_0156; Film: 16mm
    - Quemoy (3), lewis_f_jr_0157; Film: 16mm
    - Quemoy (4), lewis_f_jr_0158; Film: 16mm
    - Quemoy (5), lewis_f_jr_0159; Film: 16mm
    - Quemoy (6), 01/07/1955; lewis_f_jr_0168; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Senate Elections (1), lewis_f_jr_0171; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Senate Elections (2), 04/21/1954; lewis_f_jr_0172; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Sliste [?] (2), 1946; 1947,; 1952; lewis_f_jr_0512; Film: 16mm
    - Spain, lewis_f_jr_0454; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Spain, lewis_f_jr_0468; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Spain, lewis_f_jr_0473; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Spain, lewis_f_jr_0506; Note on the old leader reads: “Fulton Lewis (No. 12), Washington video”.; Film: 16mm
    - Spain (1), lewis_f_jr_0173; Film: 16mm
    - Spain (2), lewis_f_jr_0174; Film: 16mm
    - Spain (3), lewis_f_jr_0175; Film: 16mm
    - Spain (4), lewis_f_jr_0176; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Spain (5), lewis_f_jr_0177; Film: 16mm
    - Spain (6), lewis_f_jr_0178; Film: 16mm
    - Spain (7), lewis_f_jr_0179; Film: 16mm
    - Spain (8), lewis_f_jr_0180; Film: 16mm
    - Special Weapons, 1958; lewis_f_jr_0496; Note on the leader reads: “F Lewis Jr. No. 5. Wash. Video”.; Film: 16mm
    - Stratemeyer, lewis_f_jr_0419; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Stratemeyer, lewis_f_jr_0465; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Stratemeyer - No. 6, lewis_f_jr_0420; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Stratemeyer Interview - No. 6, lewis_f_jr_0421; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Stratemeyer Interview - No. 6, lewis_f_jr_0422; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Strathmeyer (1), lewis_f_jr_0162; Film: 16mm
    - Strathmeyer (2), lewis_f_jr_0163; Film: 16mm
    - Strathmeyer (3), lewis_f_jr_0164; Film: 16mm
    - Strathmeyer (4), lewis_f_jr_0165; Film: 16mm
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0410; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural, running time 11:35
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, lewis_f_jr_0418; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Tennessee Valley Authority - Wash Video, lewis_f_jr_0415; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Tennessee Valley Authority - Wash Video, lewis_f_jr_0416; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Tennessee Valley Authority - Wash Video, lewis_f_jr_0417; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Trailer (6), 1953; lewis_f_jr_0452; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Volks Wagon, 04/11/1955; lewis_f_jr_0413; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Wash Video - "F Lewis #15; FBI #1 ", lewis_f_jr_0219; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Wash Video - "F Lewis #15; FBI #1 ", lewis_f_jr_0220; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Wash Video - "Fulton Lewis - #5"; Manpower #8, lewis_f_jr_0222; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Wash Video - "Fulton Lewis - A.D.A", lewis_f_jr_0218; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Wash Video - "Fulton Lewis - ADA, lewis_f_jr_0221; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Wash Video - "Fulton Lewis - Churchill Visit", lewis_f_jr_0223; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Wash Video - "Fulton Lewis - Indo-China", lewis_f_jr_0224; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Wash Video - "Fulton Lewis - N.I.H. - Heart" #19, lewis_f_jr_0225; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Washington Merry-Go-Round, lewis_f_jr_0160; Film: 16mm
    - The Washington Report - Gag Reel[?], lewis_f_jr_0429; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Wheels Across India, lewis_f_jr_0230; produced by A Chrysler Corporation Motion Picture; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Wheels Across India - film fragments - head, lewis_f_jr_0231; produced by A Chrysler Corporation Motion Picture; Film: 16mm, b/w (Box 167)
    - [Untitled], 1954; lewis_f_jr_0414; produced by General Teleradio; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0424; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural, running time 11:55
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0431; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0445; Film: 16mm, b/w, silent
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0453; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0459; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0464; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0466; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0479; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0481; produced by General Teleradio, KIEM TV; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - [Untitled], 1948;1968; lewis_f_jr_0491; Film: 16mm, b/w, silent
    - [Untitled], 1948;1968; lewis_f_jr_0492; Film: 16mm, b/w, silent
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0493; Film: 16mm, b/w, silent
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0494; Film: 16mm, b/w, silent
    - [Untitled], lewis_f_jr_0495; Film: 16mm, b/w, silent
    - [Untitled] (Sound trail work print), lewis_f_jr_0501; Handwritten note in the middle of the reel reads: “Survive so to speak pix inserted”.; Film: 16mm; running time 10:30
  - Phonodiscs
    Some phonodiscs are boxes, others are individually shelved. Please request by title, box number (if given), and ID number (e.g., lewis_f_jr_0395).
    - Broadcast Murder; Ships, lewis_f_jr_0395; produced by RCA Victor Home Recording Record; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Christmas Carol Program by Hollywood Junior Choir, Parts 2 & 5, 12/22/1948; lewis_f_jr_0380; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Christmas Carol Program by Hollywood Junior Choir, Parts 2 & 5, 12/22/1948; lewis_f_jr_0381; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Christmas carols with organ and chimes, featuring Charles R. Cronham, organist, lewis_f_jr_0394; produced by Mercury; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 1 and 3, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0320; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 1 and 3, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0321; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 1 and 3, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0322; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 1 and 3, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0323; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 1 and 3, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0324; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 1 and 3, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0325; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0326; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0327; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0328; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0329; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0330; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0331; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0332; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0333; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0334; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0335; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0336; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0337; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0338; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0339; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0340; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0341; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - Christmas Eve Program by Betsy & Buddy Lewis, Parts 2 and 4, 1948; lewis_f_jr_0342; VinylDisc (Box 164)
    - City National Bank & Trust Co. of Columbus, lewis_f_jr_0389; produced by WHKC; Panacoustic, U. J. Recording Company; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Fulton Lewis Jr., 02/20/1947; lewis_f_jr_0400; produced by Universal Recording Corp.; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Fulton Lewis Jr., 02/21/1947; lewis_f_jr_0401; produced by Universal Recording Corp.; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Fulton Lewis Jr. No. 15, attempted expulsion form Southern states coop., 08/14/1947; lewis_f_jr_0405; produced by Universal Recording Corp.; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Fulton Lewis Jr. No. 3, F. U. G. T. A., 02/24/1947; lewis_f_jr_0402; produced by Universal Recording Corp.; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Fulton Lewis Jr. No. 4, Murray Lincolns Tele. Ntea. reply, 02/25/1947; lewis_f_jr_0403; produced by Universal Recording Corp.; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Fulton Lewis Jr. No. 5, Southern states coop., 02/26/1947; lewis_f_jr_0404; produced by Universal Recording Corp.; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Fulton Lewis Jr. w/ Sen. Joe. McCarthy, air check from MBS orig. Washington D.C., 03/11/1954; lewis_f_jr_0407; produced by WWDC; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Fulton Lewis Speech I, Sect. 9, Mullendore, lewis_f_jr_0390; Oct 8 [no year]; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Fulton Lewis Theme, 07/13/1951; lewis_f_jr_0388; produced by WWDC; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Fulton Lewis, Jr. from WOL - MBS feed (6:00-6:15 pm), Parts 1 & 3 (Disc 1 of 3), 09/17/1946; lewis_f_jr_0391; produced by The Voice of Washington WOL, a Cowles Station; note on the label reads: For Reference Purpose only.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Fulton Lewis, Jr. from WOL - MBS feed (6:00-6:15 pm), Part 2 (Disc 2 of 3), 09/17/1946; lewis_f_jr_0392; produced by The Voice of Washington WOL, a Cowles Station; note on the label reads: For Reference Purpose only.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Fulton Lewis, Jr. from WOL - MBS feed (6:00-6:15 pm), Part 2 (Disc 3 of 3), 09/17/1946; lewis_f_jr_0393; produced by The Voice of Washington WOL, a Cowles Station; note on the label reads: For Reference Purpose only.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Fulton Lewis, Jr. MBS, Parts 1 & 3 (Disc 1 of 2), 09/17/1946; lewis_f_jr_0384; produced by United States Recording Co.; WOL; note on label reads: Copied from WOL recording.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Fulton Lewis, Jr. MBS, Parts 2 & 4 (Disc 2 of 2), 09/17/1946; lewis_f_jr_0385; produced by United States Recording Co.; WOL; note on label reads: Copied from WOL recording.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Fulton Lewis, Part 1 & 3 (Disc 1 of 2), 12/24/1945; lewis_f_jr_0382; produced by United States Recording Co.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Fulton Lewis, Part 2 & 4 (Disc 2 of 2), 12/24/1945; lewis_f_jr_0383; produced by United States Recording Co.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Good Housekeeping Magazine: Pierre Salinger interview about Jacqueline Kennedy; Good Housekeeping Magazine: Pierre Salinger interview about International Affairs and current California political scene, 08/16/1966; lewis_f_jr_0396; produced by MCV; VinylDisc, running time 9:40 (Box 166)
    - Harriman, 12/04/1950; lewis_f_jr_0387; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Lidy Robertson: My mother’s song, Otto Ploetz - voice, Ray Henderson - organ, lewis_f_jr_0398; Aluminum Record (Box 166)
    - Lynn Castile Show, lewis_f_jr_0386; produced by KHJ; Don Lee Broadcasting System; Lacquer discs/acetates (Box 166)
    - Nobody’s for McCarthy (But the people), lewis_f_jr_0399; label reads: Nobody’s for McCarthy (But the people), Lyrics by Pat Riot, Music by Bernard Yoh, vocal Vince Mathias.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Prog. No. 129: Way Back Home; Prog. No. 130: Way Back Home, lewis_f_jr_0408; The Voice of Information and Education; produced by U. S. Government, AFRS; VinylDisc
    - Richfield Oil Conference, Parts 1; 2 & 4, lewis_f_jr_0406; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0343; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0344; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0345; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0346; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0347; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0348; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0349; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0350; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0351; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0352; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0353; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0354; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0355; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0356; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0357; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0358; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0359; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0360; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0361; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0362; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)